Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during the
production of this show.
My Gonca, Gonca open your eyes.
Come on.
Thank Allah you are with me in my
last breath.
Sshhh.
Don't say that, don't say it.
Come on Gonca, we will return
to our tent.
Open your eyes. Come on Gonca.
Come on my rose, open your eyes.
Gonca!
Togay.
Togay!
Retreat!
Hazal.
Alps! Let's go!
Gündüz! Where are you going, nephew?
Don't you see them retreating?
Uncle! I won't stop chasing that dog!
Come on Alps!
You take care of Abdulrahman Ghazi.
Let's go.
- Gonca.
Look at me sister!
Gonca!
Bamsı Bey. Bamsı Bey. Bamsı Bey.
Abdulrahman Ghazi.
Gonca.
Mother. Mother.
Wake up mother.
Get up.
Wake up.
Alps! Take the woundeds to the tent.
Bring the dead behind.
Come on Gonca. Hold on.
Hold on Gonca.
Let's go Boran
Hold on Gonca, hold on my rose.
Hold on.
Hold on daughter.
Mother!
Stop there.
Alps!
Do you think you can dogmatise us just
because you gave us land, Osman Bey?
Hatun, your stubborness drives both sides
to cliff.
Both you and your father
are pushing my patience.
Tell your Alps to fall back.
Don't make me make a choice between my
respect for you and my Bey's command.
You trust me, but how come you still
sell horses to my enemy?
You promised trade before land. You told
us you wouldn't interfere.
We trusted you. We accepted your
invitation.
Now either you keep your promise,
or we go down together.
Alps! Appropriate the horses before
I do something crazy.
Bahadır!
Since when does Kayı Bey waylay, Osman Bey?
This is banditry.
I let you trade. I didn't let you
arm my enemy.
Do your trade. Sell your sheep, sell your
goats, sell your milk.
But do not sell horses.
Horses are Turks' weapon.
You can't sell horses. You can't sell
stallion. You can't sell weapon.
You can't sell arrow.
Take your goods and go to Inegol.
Make your trade.
I am taking these horses.
I'll give you double whatever Nicola did.
From now on, this treason will end here.
Search for treason in your tent,
Osman Bey.
As long as that betrayer lives, we won't
unite. You should know that.
Alps!
Let's go.
Come on!
My Bamsı Bey, Abdulrahman Ghazi has
been martyred.
I will find and kill that betrayer.
I'll kill that betrayer.
What betrayer are you talking about,
Bamsı Bey?
The betrayer in the tent was potter Idris.
He is dead now.
What betrayer are you talking about?
Has treason ended, Dündar Bey?
Has treason ended?
It is still in us!
I will find and kill that betrayer,
Dündar Bey.
We lost their tracks, my Bey.
Let's go back.
Come on!
Bamsı Bey, let us take Abdulrahman Ghazi
to the tent.
Come on.
Keep your hands off.
Hands off, Dündar Bey.
Alps!
Alps...
Have you seen what happened to us?
Abdulrahman Ghazi was martyred.
Abdulrahman Ghazi...
Our Abdulrahman Ghazi
was martyred, my Bey.
Who did this?
Bala is taking Gonca and the wounded Alps
to the tent.
Who did this?
Who did this?!
It's Togay, my Bey.
It's Togay.
Sons.
Do you see, Alps?
Can you see what happened?
Do you see it?
Abdulrahman Ghazi has been martyred.
Oi my Ghazi
My dear fellow.
Come on get up, Kayı's valiant.
Come on, get up, get up and stand.
Just like the previous battles.
Get up.
Stand up. Stand up.
Get on your dark horse...
and go one war to another.
Arrive to the mountains, hunt there.
Come on my Ghazi, come on.
My valiant alp.
My valiant Ghazi.
We were going to be together.
We were going to go together.
You are a martyr now.
Togay!
Abdurrahman Ghazi, my dear fellow.
You are a martyr now.
You are a martyr.
Once you died once...
This Bamsı died one thousand times.
One thousand times.
My Lord! Give this ghazi of
the ghazis....
place in your heaven.
Give this ghazi of the ghazis place
in your heaven.
My Osman.
Abdulrahman Ghazi deceased.
He is a martyr now.
Oi my Ghazi.
Go to Ucmag(heaven).
Alps!
Abdulrahman Ghazi lodged like a caravan...
And now he moved, he is gone.
He left me alone here.
Abdulrahman Ghazi was a heirloom.
Now...
Now you have arrived at the rank of
shahada.
Now...
Now we have to...
take revenge.
Can I come in?
Come.
Have the caravan arrived in Inegol?
Osman Bey waylaid and took the horses.
Ahh Osman Bey ahh!
If only you knew my intentions are good!
If only you could reveal the betrayer
in your tent!
At that time we would destroy that
infidel's castle together!
But no.
What are we going to do father?
Osman Bey doesn't know it. He is angry.
He let us take goods to Inegol, but
appropriated the horses.
It seems difficult to take the castle
down now.
It's time I met Osman Bey.
Let me go with you my father.
- Get alps ready.
- As you command.
Umur Bey sent what we wanted, but it's not
good that Osman appropriated the horses.
Do you think I care about
the horses, Helen?
I do not need horses to fight, I only need
two tents' alps to fall in each other.
Osman's banditry must have made
Umur Bey furious.
While they are messing with each other,
we will complete our things in Sogut.
When Kalanoz joins, Helen,
it will be over.
Sir, a Mongol wants to see you.
- Who is he?
- He said he brought news from Togay.
Let him in.
Doors!
The wedding was ruined, so was Osman's
dignity.
Who are you?
Geyhatu's Commander Camuha.
Camuha.
Where is Togay?
Commander Togay is on his way to Konya.
It was reported that some Lords didn't
pay their taxes to Seljuqs.
Camuha, I do not talk politics with
people I don't know.
Ah Abdulrahman Ghazi.
You said shahada even in the wedding.
My time has also come.
From now on, I, too, want to be a martyr.
My Bey!
Why do you want to become a martyr?
I'll see my prophet.
Then, I'll see my brothers.
I'll see Doğan, I'll see my Ertugrul Bey.
Then I'll see my children.
I'll see my Aybars, Aslıhan,
I'll see my Hafza.
This is what it is, Cerkutay.
Some come, some go.
My Bey.
In old times...
When an important man died...
people used to be sacrificed...
to accompany his soul.
If you die, I'll sacrifice
all the enemies.
Cerkutay, we Muslims don't do that
We donate to the poors so that...
the good prayers shall accompany the
dead's soul.
I only have my armor and sword.
Nevermind, I'll sell them and feed
the poor.
They will pray for you, my Bey.
Oi Cerkutay, Oi Cerkutay.
What am I going to do with you?
Son, you have a huge heart.
What a huge heart you have!
You don't need wealth.
The face you see is Geyhatu's.
Now listen to me in view of this fact.
Osman wasn't in the wedding caravan.
The lovers' nupital was wasted.
Oldish Abdurrahman died.
The heirlooms he was supported by
are dying one by one.
Now it is Umur Bey's tent's turn.
Togay didn't say that.
What's the rush?
Geyhatu commanded us to
finish this at once...
and conquer Sogut, found a headquarters.
Did you say Sogut?
We have a lot to do.
You and your soldiers must be tired.
Now that you are the face of Geyhatu...
then I want to host you well.
Commander Mikis.
Lead our guests to their rooms.
Give a feast for them.
This is no good, we were about to
corner Umur Bey.
Togay is missing.
Nicola...
if Mongols conquer Sogut, we won't
have the power anymore.
- I won't let them.
- How?
I will make Osman attack on Mongols
like Togay is here.
When Togay comes back, he will neither be
able to found a headquarters in Sogut...
nor attack Umur Bey.
Smart move, that's what I like.
What happened here?
It smells bad news.
This is dog Togay or Nicola's job!
Apply this salve
May it work out inshallah.
My Gonca?
Thank Allah.
We stopped the bleeding.
You'll get better inshallah.
Thank you my Bala.
Having a wedding while in a war could
be like this at most.
You'll have better days.
Can I come in?
Come.
Boranalp, you take the watch.
I told you we could fight and have
a wedding.
But you didn't say that we'd do
both at the same time.
The wedding is a pretext.
The man and woman comes together,
guests have fun.
However, when two lovers come together,
each day becomes a wedding day.
Get rest.
Vengenace is my job.
Thank Allah our enemy is apparent.
Once Osman Bey commands us...
blood will drip out of my sword.
I swear I will bury a Mongol for
each sigh you have.
Bala Hatun.
What happened?
Who attacked you?
Who can it be?
Who is our enemy?
Togay and Nicola's soldiers who you tried
to sell horses came together...
and raided our wedding caravan.
Bala Hatun, it's not like how it seems.
Where is Osman Bey?
I want to see him.
They are burying martyr Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Abdurrahman Ghazi ha?
Yes, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Oh, Abdurrahman Ghazi, oh.
My Bey, Osman Bey has arrived.
He is in his tent.
I'll see Osman Bey, give him
my condolences.
Alaca, if Hatuns need any help...
Malhun Hatun.
It's not necessary. We'll take care of
our own.
We only need you to not work with
the betrayers.
Why did you let her talk like that,
Malhun Hatun?
Their pain is fresh. It's not
the right time.
Can I come in Osman Bey?
Come.
My condolences, Osman Bey.
I heard about Abdurrahman Ghazi.
He was my Ghazi father's fellow.
He lost his arm to protect our tent.
Now he died for my alps.
My condolences again, Osman Bey.
I feel you.
Togay raided the wedding caravan.
He'll pay for this eventually, Osman Bey.
What about you, Umur Bey?
What am I supposed to pay for?
Soldiers of Nicola who you made trade
were also there.
They helped Togay.
Do you know that?
I only made a trade agreement with
Nicola.
Moreover, Nicola didn't recieve
the horses.
I don't trust Nicola's friendship or
loyalty. I don't vouch for him!
Nicola is my biggest enemy.
What are you talking about?
He attacked today, I will attack tomorrow.
There will be a bloodshed.
You are trying to make trades in this
bloodshed!
Osman Bey, attacking a wedding caravan
is lowness, of course!
But we are not the ones who are to
prevent that.
The land is yours.
You have the responsibility.
You are right. This is my land.
This is my responsibilty.
Vengeance is mine!
But, it's too late for Nicola.
I will not show mercy if someone gets
between us, even my fellows.
Who can put you off from taking
your rightous revenge?
We are ready to help.
I have spoken.
Just get out of my way, that's enough.
Get down.
I brought news from Lord Nicola.
I want to see Osman Bey.
Go.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
My Bey, Nicola sent a messenger.
Take him in.
The head infidel Nicola...
reveals where Togay is hiding.
He says he has nothing to do with
the raid...
and he is not with Togay anymore.
We can't trust him.
This is a new game of Nicola's, Osman Bey.
Did this guy just want to be our friend
out of nothing?
I know this is a trap.
But we'll go anyways.
Where are we going to go, Osman Bey?
To a trap?
We will, brother. We will.
We will take precautions and go.
Because we have no other option.
I'll chase every chance that can give
me Togay.
I don't think Nicola would set up such
an obvious trick.
Maybe it's right that they fell in
each other with Togay.
But we have to be sure
about it, Osman Bey.
We'll see, brother, we'll see.
But first, we have to go.
Get alps ready.
Command is yours, Osman Bey.
This is Nicola's payment for our goods,
my Bey.
Good job, Bahadır.
Eyvallah (thank you).
You can get out now.
We will continue making trades with Nicola
to infiltrate in Inegol Castle.
What about Osman Bey?
He sees us as a betrayer, just like
all the Kayı tents.
This bothers me too.
We were held responsible for the
raid...
to the wedding caravan.
Why are you not telling our real intention
to sell Nicola the horses, my Bey?
Even though we are seen as a betrayer
in front of Osman Bey and his tent...
we can't reveal our game.
As long as we can't reveal that betrayer
in Kayı...
We can't explain our intentions.
Then, Nikola will find out our goal.
The owner of the thumb ring is still in
the tribe and Osman Bey is accusing us.
Don't worry. The time is coming
for that traitor.
They are getting ready
to march, my bey.
They are many. It looks like they
are going for a raid.
But...
...we couldn't see Togay, my bey.
If his warriors are here, he must
be around.
Brother, I will finish Togay off,
and you will take the warriors.
Don't worry. None will survive.
Come on.
Alps!
For Abdurrahman Ghazi!
A trap!
Where are you Togay?
When Togay returns, I'll give
your head to him, Osman!
Togay, where are you?
Alps! We are returning.
Come on!
-Brother.
-Nikola's news were true.
But the commander of these
pagan mongols...
...Togay isn't here.
Where might he be, Osman Bey?
When Togay returns, I will
give your head to him!
The mongol that ran away said
'When Togay returns'.
It's apparent that he isn't around.
But Nikola's news show that they
don't have a true alliance.
What's on your mind, my bey?
We'll break that tie.
They'll take each others' heads.
How did Osman find us so easily?
According to the information Commander
Togay gave, there is only one way to find out.
We are going to Söğüt.
Camuha...you?
What are you doing here?
Petros, did you tell Togay's
location?
-No...
-Who then?
-I don't know.
-Dündar!
Only Dündar can know that.
If you have the shadow of
treason on you...
...Togay's sword will behead you.
Why would we betray...
...both our target is Osman.
Our path is stony.
If you think it's hard, your death
won't be easy either.
You'll write a letter for Dündar.
When Togay finds out that it was
Nikola, they'll alliance will break.
If Nikola sold Togay out,
he must have a reason.
We'll use this opportunity. We won't
stop, we'll pursue.
We'll run through these lands and
tear Togay apart.
-Inshallah.
-Togay deserved what's coming.
But, Osman Bey, we need to
take care of Nikola first.
Bamsı Bey is right. If we take care of
Nikola first, Togay will be an easy prey.
We have the strength to beat
them both, thank Allah.
We have the strength, thank Allah.
And we have the passion.
The conquest of İnegöl will be easier
with the support of the beys.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come.
-Brother.
-I congratulate your efforts, brother.
Thank you, brother.
Welcome.
-But you are early.
-I have important news, brother.
Tell me.
I got information from a merchant
from Constantinople.
Brother of Kalamos that you killed
is coming to İnegöl with great numbers.
They'll reach the castle tomorrow
evening.
-Then, we don't have time.
-We should act at once, Bamsı Bey.
It seems that Nikola is
worried about his life.
He knows that İnegöl will fall.
Beys, this news is important.
Before İnegöl's conquest gets harder,
we should be on the battlefield.
You have the sword of jihad, Osman Bey.
Just say the word.
We'll be there at once.
Thank you, Bamsı Bey.
Thank you.
-Thank you, brother.
We'll stop them before reaching
the castle.
Inform the tribe beys. They should
come with a few alps.
If not with numbers, why do you
want them to come, Osman Bey?
They'll get a taste of the jihad.
They should get used to the
idea of unity.
Brother, I want the beys and
the alps ready at the dawn.
Don't worry. We'll bring them
all to the battlefield.
Thank you. The conquest of İnegöl
depends on cutting this support.
We'll hit the heathens
as hard as we can.
Sir, do you think that Osman trusted
us and attacked Camuha?
A wolf pursues the prey even
if it's dangerous.
Even if he didn't see Togay there,
he must've killed Camuha and his men.
Who knows? Maybe they killed
each other already.
What if Camuha is alive?
Togay will find out that you
were behind this.
According to what Camuha said, Mongols
will use the Seljuks...
...to collect taxes through
the new lord.
Mongols...
The only thing they care about is taxes.
They don't care about the Seljuks or Byzantines.
Kalanoz will be here tomorrow.
I'll have not only Söğüt...
...but the honor of killing Togay.
Kalanoz must be running here to get
the revenge of his brother.
Those who chase revenge are
rebellious.
I will control Kalanoz's anger for
my victory.
I was awaiting you, Dündar Bey.
Won't you tell me what happened?
They were silent for a long time, woman.
Now, they are calling me.
Süleyman?
Both Osman and the Pope's dogs
think that they use me.
But I used them.
This took too long, Dündar Bey.
This isn't good.
We should cut it off, woman.
I should behead the one in between
me and the throne.
I know, you are afraid.
And you are right.
The doomsday is close.
So, I'll get Togay to their hands.
Don't forget what happened
with Balgay.
I have nothing else to lose
but my head, woman.
I want you to go to Kastamonu.
I shouldn't look behind
at the doomsday.
If we'll die, we'll die together,
Dündar Bey.
Together and upright.
How will you find Togay?
After Osman's attack, he will find me.
I will blow my last strike to Osman
with Togay.
Inshallah.
Bala.
What happened to Gonca Hatun
makes you sad.
Her wound is healing, my bey.
But what happened there...
Don't keep it in you.
Share it with me, Bala.
I'm afraid to give you trouble, my bey.
Come.
Words words can only heal me.
Osman.
Gonca and Boran Alp hardly
found any time to marry.
And they were attacked at
that wedding.
When we think such things happen...
...we'll await attacks
at every moment.
Osman Bey, this endless war...
...if it stops us from doing
weddings...
...celebrations, funerals...
...we can't expand, reproduce...
...build families.
You spoke like a Khatun.
You are right.
You are right, Bala.
But this is the fate of the people...
...who aims to break chains...
...and build a state for
the oppressed.
My mission is to save my tribe
from this fire.
We'll have good days, Bala.
We'll have good days.
Our children will grow up
in peace.
We'll have weddings and
holidays.
Our elders, sisters won't
be have to go to wars.
We'll have an army.
We'll have a state.
We will.
We will, Bala.
Inshallah, my bey.
Inshallah.
-If you allow me.
-Of course.
We will.
Dumur Bey's Tribe
What will we do now, my bey?
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come, my daughter.
-You summoned me, my bey.
-Osman Bey...
Osman Bey still doesn't recognize me.
He neglects the blood I spilled for my
country, my sons that I sacrificed...
-What happened, my bey?
-He doesn't even want to hear...
...how I stood straight against
the armies of Geyhatu.
Now, it's time he finds out.
He wants me to shepherd my people
like his lambs.
It's time to show our fangs.
-What are you saying, father?
-Osman Bey...
...is preparing for jihad.
He invited all the tribes except us.
He's trying to ruin our reputation
in front of the other tribes.
-That's what it's all about.
-We can't let that happen, father.
Of course, we won't.
Malhun, go to Osman Bey
with Bahadır.
Let them know who we are.
Osman Bey, you can't harm my honor.
-Who are you?
-Togay's shadow, Camuha.
Speak.
Osman raided you, so you want
to know who sold you out, huh?
Speak.
You should kill Osman, not me.
Speak!
It's Nikola who sold you out.
Togay must've forgot to feed Nikola.
Nikola wants us to face the Kayıs.
Why is he doing that?
It seems like they choose Umur bey
as a friend.
If Togay had informed me, I would
tell him everything.
If Togay had trusted me, you wouldn't
lose all your warriors.
Wait for a word from Togay.
-May Allah bless your efforts, Osman Bey.
-Thank you, Bala. Thank you.
Osman Bey, alps are waiting for you
with Savcı Bey.
-Thank you, brother.
-Turkmen Beys are also waiting.
Come on. Let us be on our way.
We heard that you are going to a jihad,
Osman Bey. My father wants us to join.
We have enough alps, Malhun Hatun.
Now, we need to be on our way at once.
Are you denying us the jihad, Osman Bey?
You should stand in front of those
who are going to a jihad.
What are your intentions, Osman Bey?
You are stopping our trade,
you are stopping our jihad...
...did you invite us to these borderlands
to sit like elders?
I invited you to support me,
not to defy me.
I invited you to be my ally,
not to be my enemy.
Should I focus on you or the
enemy on the battlefield?
Now, get out of my way.
Malhun Hatun. Come and drink
something with me.
Let us talk woman to a woman.
Come on!
Hold!
Commander, follow me with the archers.
Scout the way ahead. Inform the army.
Forward.
We have news from the scouts.
The Byzantines will come through Karakuş Hill.
Commander Kalamoz is coming with
his vanguards...
...ahead of his army.
My bey, is a realitive of Lord Kalamoz
that you killed before?
It's his brother.
He seeks revenge.
He'll burn in his own fire.
We'll fight for Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Thank you.
My beys, we'll attack them
at the Valley of Kördüğüm.
This is the battlefield.
Brother Gündüz, you will attack
from these hills.
Brother Savcı, you will go through
this road.
Don't worry, Osman Bey.
Bamsı Bey, you will lead the archers.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
We'll pierce them. Don't worry.
Thank you.
And I will face Kalamoz.
The army that the emperor sent with
Kalamoz is coming to take our homes.
It's our duty to stop them from
reaching the castle.
-May Allah help us.
-Amin!
May Allah bless our efforts.
Come on.
Is that so? He has enough alps, huh?
I guessed it. He is trying to
harm our reputation...
...and make us look like traitors in
front of the other beys.
Don't worry, my father. Everyone knows
how loyal you are to Turkish traditions.
But...
...are you sure that you don't want to
speak about your trade with Nikola?
Of course, I am.
Osman Bey won't know this.
He won't, so that...
...Nikola won't know my real
intentions.
While he is busy with Kalamoz and
Togay...
...we will conquer İnegöl Castle.
Bahadır! Come here.
How are the beys who rallied
to Osman's help?
They need help, my bey.
They are all in bad conditions.
They are far from doing the trade they
hoped but they are helping Osman.
Everyone was sad because of the
death of Dervish Zülfikar.
And they were attacked on
their way back, my sheik.
The bride is wounded on her chest,
and the groom is in his heart.
The path of love is difficult,
Dervish Akça.
The people of Söğüt are affected.
Shopkeepers are worried.
Are the intentions of the shopkeepers
and the dervishes are different, Kumral Abdal?
They both buy and sell, my sheik.
I understand the shopkeepers but what
do dervishes buy and sell?
They sell their desires and buy
the approval of Allah.
Do you see, Akça?
Dervishes trade too.
And both the dervishes and the shopkeepers
seek peace.
May I enter, my sheik?
Peace...
Come, my daughter.
If the peace has come,
we should leave, my sheik.
Bala, my heart.
My eyes, come, sit.
Father.
Allah gave the opportunity and
I ran to you.
I'm thankful for that mighty
and good Allah.
Tell me, what are you doing?
I'm busy with the tribe's works.
Osman Bey is on jihad.
He wants to punish
the attackers.
Ghazis also do trade, my daughter.
They buy and sell lives,
with Allah's approval.
They become ghazis by taking and
martyrs by giving.
Bala, tell me.
What is the real matter?
My sheik, Osman Bey's
only trouble isn't the heathens.
The people he thinks to be friends,
make troubles and they complain.
Umur Bey is a valiant Turkmen bey...
...who has swung his sword against
the pagan Mongols for all his life.
Osman Bey is a commander of
ghazis...
...who try to proselytize Allah's religion
with his bare sword on these lands.
But Umur Bey and his daughter
Malhun Hatun.
Muslims are worried about their future
in between the Mongols and the Rums.
They can't bear a fight between
beys.
This can't go on.
Hold!
Archers will hold this hill.
We are close to Turkish lands.
Osman ambushed the last army.
We'll be cautious.
Archers!
Kalamoz!
You came for revenge!
I'm here! Come on!
Osman! God damn it!
Archers, shoot!
Shoot!
Alps!
Protect Osman Bey!
Alps! For Allah!
Kalanoz.
If you don't talk...
Brother.
Bamsı Bey.
- Some of the soldiers ran away, my Bey.
- They can't run away, brother.
Are we going to follow them?
Mongols will kill them before they
arrive at the castle.
Spirits want blood!
For our dead soldiers...
for Togay...
don't feel pity! Kill them all!
We won't let them run away!
Mongols, huh?
They knew Nikola told me where they hid.
We killed many of their soldiers.
They want to take revenge on Nikola.
Didn't we kill the soldiers?
That's why they sent my brother the news
via a merchant from Constantin.
We didn't set a trap for Kalanoz.
Mongols did.
Nice.
Let them kill each other.
While the jackals fight, the lion
comes out.
They both will serve us.
Until I rip their lungs off.
Give the Beys their prizes.
They will get what they deserve.
Thank you.
Kalanoz's soldiers are wretched.
He is an intelligent commander
even he has been trapped.
He took his soldiers and
went to the forest.
He saved himself even though most of
his soldiers are dead.
What about...
the Beys who came to support Osman Bey?
Osman Bey is an intelligent
soldier, my Bey.
They came with their Alps.
He says...
he can win a victory without us.
However...
he doesn't want to deprive us of
the war's good deed.
Their tent is in a difficult
situation, my Bey.
From now on, each Alp that Osman Bey wants
will put them in a difficult situation.
What are you thinking, my Bey?
I want to invite all of the Beys
to my tent.
Send news to them.
Your command, my Bey.
Osman Bey deprives us of the honor
of the war.
However, we will stand by the Beys who are
also in the war.
We will save them from Osman Bey.
We will show them they are not alone.
Kalanoz lost most of his soldiers.
This means that İnegöl won't get
a help.
Nikola and Togay being enemies...
makes our work easier and possible.
Turkmen Beys kept their promises.
Osman Bey, as you know...
war is war, prize is a prize.
Turkmen Beys wait for it now.
It is a religious duty to be in the war...
however, we need to relieve their wounds.
We should support them
and make them happy.
Beys are right, Osman Bey.
All of them have a responsibility
for their own tent.
I know about their conditions.
From the day I drive union politics...
I know what they need and what they lack.
I know their financial
conditions are bad.
However, they don't want
to expose themselves.
- Uncle.
- Yes, my Bey.
Send news to merchants and craftsmen.
Make up the needs of everyone...
who came to the war or not.
They should see me for the count.
They will get more if they help.
Send news to Beys, too. They should
come to my tent.
They should see that I didn't
invite them just for the war.
We will help them if they need anything.
We will relieve their wounds.
They will see our union's power
and benefits.
So that, when we say there is a war...
they should help us with love and
eagerness.
Thank you.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
My Bala.
I heard you talk, my Bey.
Are there many martyrs?
The victory is of Muslim Turks, my Bala.
Our martyrs are in heaven.
Of course, they are, my Osman.
However, I want to help the ones rest.
I love your beautiful heart.
Hatun of Kayı.
Who will relieve the wounds of children
and Hatuns, other than you?
I have been serving you for years.
I've seen your childhood.
The times that you were a little girl.
Your martyr brothers and
your mother loved you.
My brothers are martyrs.
Now I'm responsible for my tent.
You've changed.
My hands are callused because
of the swords.
And my heart.
Alaca Hatun.
- Am I arrogant?
- If you're asking this, no.
Am I being unfair...
to a man who struggles for our good?
Who are you talking about?
Osman Bey, Bey of Kayı.
We want him to find the traitor.
We pressure a man...
who have got into a war with
both Rums and Mongols...
and who tries his best for his tent.
That's because we don't want
any problem, Malhun Hatun.
- Who are you, Hatun?
- Malhun Hatun, daughter of Umur Bey.
Daughter of Umur Bey?
We're coming here.
Our fate is up to you.
However, we are crowded.
10.000 people will come.
Can you handle it?
Look for the traitor
in your own tent, Osman Bey.
We won't be united as long as
the traitor is alive.
Keep that in mind.
You save your tent well, Osman Bey!
We trusted in your words.
Is that your promise?
Don't say things that you don't want to.
You're angry.
My anger isn't related to that, Osman Bey.
What confuses my mind is that I
have trusted you.
I should've not trusted you.
I know who to suspect
as long as you don't bring him.
Don't you trust my word, Malhun Hatun?
My father, who trusted you...
is wounded now.
I know you're angry.
However, we have the same enemy.
They want to set us against
each other, obviously.
You're in trouble, Osman Bey.
How will you handle it?
We want him to find the traitor.
However, we hide stuff from him.
I think we're being
unfair to a valiant Bey.
What kind of hell is this, Nikola?
How come İnegöl is like that?
- Do you understand me now, Kalanoz?
- Turks attacked me and my army.
And Mongols killed my
soldiers who ran away.
I know everything.
How could you make Turks and
Mongols friends, Nikola?
What you have to learn first
on these lands is...
that no one will be friends, Kalanoz.
We can't guess who will destroy who.
I'm a soldier, Nikola!
I'm not a politician.
I just want you to show
me the right target.
Let me be sure who is
my friend or foe.
I will show you how to take Söğüt.
And you will take your brother's revenge.
My Alps.
do you know...
why I hit you?
They killed the lord.
We...
You could've taken measures
on the road, right?
You could've protected the lord...
with your shields, right?
You could've done better, right?
You're right, my Bey.
It won't happen again.
Everyone makes mistakes.
However...
not again.
My Alps.
My valiants.
My brothers.
Brother.
Don't worry.
We'll take revenge on Togay.
Yes, my Bey.
I know.
However, I have a request.
Tell me.
When we have him, I want to kill him.
My Bey.
We did what you said. We let all the Beys
know. However...
- What?
- Umur Bey.
- He sent news to the Beys.
- So?
The Beys will obey him and participate
in the meeting.
Get the horses ready.
Let's see...
- what Umur Bey wants to do.
- Yes, my Bey.
Alps, come on!
Send my regards to Osman Bey and Umur Bey.
They are both my guests.
However, don't tell
Osman Bey that Umur Bey is coming and...
don't tell Umur Bey that
Osman Bey is coming.
Your command, my Sheikh.
As you command...
we will bring them here without
knowing each other come.
Let's end the separation already.
They should unite, my Sheikh.
So that they can reach what they want.
Umur Bey's tent
We know that there is always a
war in those lands...
and there are always martyrs.
Those martyrs are our martyrs. Ghazis are
our ghazis.
It's our responsibility to
support their families.
What are these golds?
They are
what Ghazi and martyr families deserve.
Even if Osman Bey doesn't give me and
my tent the honor of war...
he can't prevent me from
supporting my brothers.
My brothers, why do you doubt?
It's what you deserve.
Umur Bey, Osman has a right to have an
attitude against you.
It's not okay
to trade with Nikola, Umur Bey.
My brothers...
Osman Bey misunderstood me.
And you misunderstood me.
I want you to know that...
Umur Bey, son of Kızıl Bey,
has never been a traitor!
My brothers, your tents have needs.
How will you meet your needs without
trading?
We have to trade to live on
in these lands.
- Even Osman Bey has to trade.
- Tell me, Umur Bey.
What does Osman Bey have to do?
You came in without my
permission, Osman Bey.
And you ask me questions.
Answer me.
I'm sure you have one.
Tell me, then.
Shouldn't be Beys helping each other in
difficult situations?
Or do you consider this to be too much?
I have invited them to the war.
I will look after Ghazi's rights.
Is Kayı Tent incapable of helping
their brothers?
No, what kind
of words are they, Osman Bey?
Right words!
The words of
Osman Bey, son of Ertuğrul Ghazi!
Father.
Osman Bey did it again.
He will see us as his enemies now.
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
My Bey.
From Sheikh Edebali.
You deceived me. You let Togay
go over me.
You should be happy
that you're alive, Dündar Bey.
As you don't tell us Osman's intention...
you don't stand by us.
I'm sick of your betrayals
and plays, Süleyman.
I want to live peacefully in my lands
and take what is mine.
I have done what you say until today.
Now, it's your turn.
Wow.
So, Dündar Bey doesn't trust us anymore.
Osman will die.
You will be with me or you
will die with me.
Then...
let's talk and clear up the
problem, Dündar Bey.
Who starts up in anger
sits down with a loss, brother.
Tell us.
What do you want to do?
My Bey. The
families of martyrs are waiting for you.
Wait for my news.
Not Nikola, not Togay.
We will do it three of us.
Wait for my news.
Will we trust him?
We will act like it...
until the day I kill him.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful)
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam, Osman Bey.
Come.
It's an honor.
Not at all, my Sheikh.
You summoned me.
I came here quickly.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful)
May Allah rest our martyrs in peace.
May Allah grant you what you want.
Amin, my Sheikh.
We have talked that the Islam community
is in separation.
And we know what Muslims...
are going through.
Now, I know that Turkmen
Beys are separated.
My Sheikh.
- Salam Alaikum, my Sheikh.
- Alaikum Salam, Umur Bey.
Alaikum Salam.
Welcome, it's an honor.
- It's an honor for me, my Sheikh.
- Come.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful)
If Turkmen Beys stood against Mongols...
instead of standing against each other...
would you migrate to Bithynia, Umur Bey?
Who can devastate Turks
other than Turks, my Sheikh?
That's why we invited our Beys.
Our property...
isn't at the center of Turk land.
We are on the Byzantine border.
What we take and...
what we give is with Byzantine.
The Turk's enemy is obvious.
It is...
Byzantine.
They ally if needed.
Mongols attack us when
we arrive the lands.
My Beys.
I see that...
you think the same about Turk's aim
and freedom.
Then, we should disappoint the ones...
who want to harm us.
The people believe that on Osman
Bey's property...
Turkmen tents are peaceful and together.
They are happy.
The enemies should know
that the Turkmen tents...
support Osman Bey.
They should be afraid.
Thank you.
You're right, my Sheikh.
However...
Osman Bey...
may Allah save us...
Osman Bey sees us as traitors.
We have told him that the traitor is...
closer to him than us.
- My Sheikh.
- Umur Bey...
You are in the presence of our Sheikh.
Tell us clearly.
Who is the traitor closer to me
than you are?
As you imply that you know something...
then tell him and Osman Bey won't...
suspect you again.
The owner of this thumb ring... (thumb ring used
to draw the bow in the ottoman empire.)
is the same person as the person
who shot the potter.
The engraving on it...
shows that it is someone
close to you, Osman Bey.
My Sheikh.
Uncle Dündar.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com